
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Java is a type of :",
    answer: "Object Oriented Programming Language",
    options: [
      "Object Based Programming Language",
      "Object Oriented Programming Language",
      "Object type Programming Language",
      "Object Orientd Based Programming Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Java Compiler compiles the file(Source Code) in :",
    answer: ".class extension",
    options: [
      ".object extension",
      ".byte extension",
      ".java extension",
      ".class extension"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Unlike C++ java does not support?",
    answer: "Operator Overloading",
    options: [
      "Reference Variable",
      "Hierarchy level Inheritance",
      "Operator Overloading",
      "All Of These"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What happened when we create multiple objects in java which are not used?",
    answer: "Garbage collector collect the objects and nothing happens",
    options: [
      "Java ignores them and move ahead",
      "It throws an error",
      "Garbage collector collect the objects and nothing happens",
      "Java use interpreter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Types Of arrays on the basis of size in java:",
    answer: "Static array and Dynamic Array",
    options: [
      "Static array and Dynamic Array",
      "Because Java arrays store in continuous memory so Static array",
      "Java Might use Linked List but it has only Static Arrays",
      "Java Supports Multidimensional arrays and so it is static"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Java Uses ____ for encoding the Characters ?",
    answer: "UTF - 16 Unicode Transformation Format",
    options: [
      "ASCII - American Standard code for information interchange",
      "UTF - 16 Unicode Transformation Format",
      "Java is a high level programming language use UTF-16 and ASCII",
      "Java does Not support UTF -16 because of 16 bits to store character"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Why Choose Java instead Of C++",
    answer: "Java uses UTF-16 and have memory management,Exceptional Handling,Garbage collector",
    options: [
      "Java has support of backend development",
      "Java Follow Object oriented Programming",
      "Java uses UTF-16 and have memory management,Exceptional Handling,Garbage collector",
      "Object Orientd Based Programming Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Strings In java are",
    answer: "String Java, Both have Immutable as well Mutable String.",
    options: [
      "Mutable Generally",
      "Immutable Generally ",
      "Mutable Generally But we can make it by Using Constructors",
      "String Java, Both have Immutable as well Mutable String."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "If we compare Two Strings in Java we use which of these to get desired output",
    answer: "We should Use S1.compareTo() function",
    options: [
      "S1 == S2",
      "S1.charAt(i)==S2.charAt(j)",
      "We should Use S1.compareTo() function",
      " Java Strings are stored in string pool so use Java S1===S2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "what happens when we does not make a public class",
    answer: "Error for not recognized",
    options: [
      "Nothing Happens, Program execute smoothly",
      "Program might be crash",
      "Exception may occured",
      "Error for not recognized"
    ]
  },
]